battleclinic.com 2016-05-12

# BattleClinic - EVE - tools - advice - forums - guides

### BattleClinic Deep Space Supply Privacy Policy

### November 2006

At BattleClinic Deep Space Supply we recognize that privacy is important. This Policy applies to all of the products, services and websites offered by BattleClinic Deep Space Supply or its subsidiaries or affiliated companies (collectively, BattleClinic Deep Space Supply's "services").

BattleClinic Deep Space Supply adheres to the US safe harbor privacy principles of Notice, Choice, Onward Transfer, Security, Data Integrity, Access and Enforcement.

If you have any questions about this Policy, please feel free to contact us through our website or write to us at Privacy Matters, c/o BattleClinic Deep Space Supply 248 3rd #825, Oakland CA 94607, USA.

### Information we collect and how we use it:

In order to provide our full range of services, we may collect the following types of information:

Information you provide - When you sign up for a BattleClinic Deep Space Supply Account or other BattleClinic Deep Space Supply service or promotion that requires registration, we ask you for personal information (such as your name, email address and an account password). 

BattleClinic Deep Space Supply cookies - When you visit BattleClinic Deep Space Supply, we send one or more cookies - a small file containing a string of characters - to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser. We use cookies to improve the quality of our service by storing user preferences and tracking user trends. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some BattleClinic Deep Space Supply features and services may not function properly if your cookies are disabled.

Log information - When you use BattleClinic Deep Space Supply services, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser.

User communications - When you send email or other communication to BattleClinic Deep Space Supply, we may retain those communications in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests and improve our services.

Affiliated sites - We may offer some of our services in connection with other web sites. Personal information that you provide to those sites may be sent to BattleClinic Deep Space Supply in order to deliver the service. We process such information in accordance with this Policy. The affiliated sites may have different privacy practices and we encourage you to read their privacy policies.

Links - BattleClinic Deep Space Supply may present links in a format that enables us to keep track of whether these links have been followed. We use this information to improve the quality of our search technology, customized content and advertising.

Other sites - This Privacy Policy applies to web sites and services that are owned and operated by BattleClinic Deep Space Supply. We do not exercise control over the sites displayed as search results or links from within our various services. These other sites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information from you.

BattleClinic Deep Space Supply only processes personal information for the purposes described in the applicable Privacy Policy and/or privacy notice for specific services. In addition to the above, such purposes include:

Providing our products and services to users, including the display of customized content and advertising; Auditing, research and analysis in order to maintain, protect and improve our services; Ensuring the technical functioning of our network; and Developing new services. 

BattleClinic Deep Space Supply processes personal information on our servers in the United States of America. In some cases, we process personal information on a server outside your own country. We may process personal information to provide our own services. In some cases, we may process personal information on behalf of and according to the instructions of a third party, such as PayPal or our suppliers.

### Choices for personal information

When you sign up for a particular service that requires registration, we ask you to provide personal information. We generally do not use this information in a manner different than the purpose for which it was collected, but we will ask for your consent prior to such use. We will not collect or use sensitive information for purposes other than those described in this Policy and/or in the specific service notices, unless we have obtained your prior consent.

You can decline to submit personal information to any of our services, in which case BattleClinic Deep Space Supply may not be able to provide those services to you.

### Information sharing

BattleClinic Deep Space Supply only shares personal information with other companies or individuals outside of BattleClinic Deep Space Supply in the following limited circumstances:

We have your consent. We require opt-in consent for the sharing of any sensitive personal information. We have a good faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to (a) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request, (b) enforce applicable Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations thereof, (c) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, or (d) protect against imminent harm to the rights, property or safety of BattleClinic Deep Space Supply, its users or the public as required or permitted by law. 

If BattleClinic Deep Space Supply becomes involved in a merger, acquisition, or any form of sale of some or all of its assets, we will provide notice before personal information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

### Information security

We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. These include internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, as well as physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store personal data.

We restrict access to personal information to BattleClinic Deep Space Supply employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our services. 

### Data integrity

BattleClinic Deep Space Supply processes personal information only for the purposes for which it was collected and in accordance with this Policy or any applicable service-specific privacy notice. We review our data collection, storage and processing practices to ensure that we only collect, store and process the personal information needed to provide or improve our services. We take reasonable steps to ensure that the personal information we process is accurate, complete, and current, but we depend on our users to update or correct their personal information whenever necessary.

### Accessing and updating personal information

When you use BattleClinic Deep Space Supply services, we make good faith efforts to provide you with access to your personal information and either to correct this data if it is inaccurate or to delete such data at your request if it is not otherwise required to be retained by law or for legitimate business purposes. We ask individual users to identify themselves and the information requested to be accessed, corrected or removed before processing such requests, and we may decline to process requests that are unreasonably repetitive or systematic, require disproportionate technical effort, jeopardize the privacy of others, or would be extremely impractical (for instance, requests concerning information residing on backup tapes), or for which access is not otherwise required. In any case where we provide information access and correction, we perform this service free of charge, except if doing so would require a disproportionate effort. Some of our services have different procedures to access, correct or delete users' personal information. 

### Enforcement

BattleClinic Deep Space Supply regularly reviews its compliance with this Policy. Please feel free to direct any questions or concerns regarding this Policy or BattleClinic Deep Space Supply's treatment of personal information by contacting us through this web site or by writing to us at Privacy Matters, c/o BattleClinic Deep Space Supply BattleClinic Deep Space Supply 248 3rd #825, Oakland CA 94607, USA. When we receive formal written complaints at this address, it is BattleClinic Deep Space Supply's policy to contact the complaining user regarding his or her concerns. We will cooperate with the appropriate regulatory authorities, including local data protection authorities, to resolve any complaints regarding the transfer of personal data that cannot be resolved between BattleClinic Deep Space Supply and an individual.

### Changes to this policy

Please note that this Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will not reduce your rights under this Policy without your explicit consent, and we expect most such changes will be minor. Regardless, we will post any Policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice (including, for certain services, email notification of Policy changes). Each version of this Policy will be identified at the top of the page by its effective date, and we will also keep prior versions of this Privacy Policy in an archive for your review.

If you have any additional questions or concerns about this Policy, please feel free to contact us any time through this web site or at Privacy Matters, c/o BattleClinic Deep Space Supply 248 3rd #825, Oakland CA 94607, USA.
